Mr. President, we asked our viewers if they had questions, here are a couple.
Jamie T. from Virginia said one of your biggest messages in campaign slogans was drain the
swamp.
But the idea that serving the American people is a privilege and not a career, and the politicians
are supposed to answer to the American people and not the opposite, when will your administration
be putting together a proposal for term limits for Congress?
Well, we're looking into that right now.
Right now, I want to get those congressmen to go and approve Obamacare and all the different
things that we're working on.
One step at a time.
We'll be doing it, really.
I mean, that's something down the road a little bit.
A lot of people don't like that, frankly, you know, they consider term limits to be
an election, but I think it would be a good thing.
But right now, what I want to do is get Obamacare approved and I want people to love us.
Approved or changed?
Well, really, well, changed when I say Obamacare, I mean, I'm talking about real change.
And I suspect the first thing that's going to change will be the name, but we're talking
about repealing and replacing.
And if we don't do that, I would be very upset.
Nobody's going to get thrown out of their insurance, are they?
Because that's what a lot of people are saying on the left.
They're saying millions of people
are gonna lose the insurance.
No, they have it all wrong,
and you're gonna hear about it during the speech,
but they have it all wrong.
We're gonna have a really great healthcare plan,
and it's gonna be much more affordable,
including for the country.
Go ahead.
Now, I know when you were inaugurated,
you put your hand on your Bible that your mother had given you as a child. I know when you were inaugurated used you put
your hand on your Bible that your mother given you as a child I know as a mother
as parents we pray for our children we want the best for them and your parents
they probably prayed for you so much but maybe not they might not have realized
that you were gonna get this far and I know they would be very proud of you
that leads me to this question Ronald wrote us and said I, I pray for you daily. Do you take time to pray?
I do, actually. And to me, it's very important. But that's so nice. Who is that?
That's Ronald.
Wow. Hello, Ronald. We ought to bring Ronald to the White House.
He'd be happy to come.
I like Ronald.
And this is the last one. Alan Sherman from Queens says, I'm a diehard New York Mets fan since you're a native of the
Great borough of Queens, but moved to Manhattan. Are you a Mets fan or a Yankees fan?
The fate of the world relies on this answer
Well, I don't think it does but actually I do like both teams and I love the Steinbrenner family and the Will Pond family and
Randy Levine and the whole group they Randy has done a terrific job he's involved
with the Yankees now you're probably gonna win New York well I don't know but
I do like both teams I really do what about Social Security people my age are
worried that it might run out by the time we need it you're gonna be okay
that was Ainsley from Manhattan